http://domainpeople.com/legal/privacy-statement.html

LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 16, 2011
DomainPeople, Inc. (“DomainPeople”) respects the privacy of its customers and visitors and is committed to protecting the personal information of its customers and visitors. This Privacy Policy covers the site http://www.domainpeople.com. We collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our site unless you choose to provide that information to us or as specifically outlined in this Policy. This Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use (“TOU”).
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the DomainPeople Legal Department at legal@domainpeople.com.
DomainPeople complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
This Policy describes our general principles for the collection and use of information from customers and visitors to our websites. We want to ensure that you understand how we will and will not use the information you entrust to us. In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Policy.
For visitors, we've structured our websites so that, in general, you can visit us on Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.
For prospective and existing customers and partners, once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with DomainPeople.
What type of information does DomainPeople collect?
When you visit our website, our Web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP's domain, the time you accessed our website, and the pages from within our website that you visit and is not personally identifiable information except as needed to prevent fraud or abuse of the system.
When you sign up for DomainPeople's services, you provide us with both contact and payment information. Contact information typically includes your name, address, and phone number. Payment information typically includes your credit card number.
While you are a DomainPeople customer, we manage information with regard to your account status, choice of services, and customer logs. In addition, we may store customers' electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications.
Surveys or Contests
From time-to-time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).
We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter.
While we may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests, DomainPeople will contractually ensure that said service provider will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.
How do we use this information?
We use the contact information you provide us to establish our service for you. We use payment information for payment processing purposes only. We create and maintain other information such as customer account status, choice of services, and customer logs in the normal course of providing service. By pressing the “submit” button, each visitor constitutes consent to use the information for purposes stated in this Policy.
DomainPeople may use customer information to provide customers with system information or information about new or upgraded products if you have chosen to receive such offers. You may opt out of receiving these offers by changing your preferences in your account information or by following the unsubscribe instructions in each email sent to you.
Our trusted affiliates are responsible for processing or handling some of the information we receive, such as order fulfillment for phone services. Those affiliates are not authorized to use such information for purposes beyond those specified by us including marketing and are required to preserve the confidentiality with which we treat such information.
We may disclose contact information with your permission when gathering and posting testimonials.
We will not otherwise disclose customer personal and account information unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of DomainPeople, our customers, or others. We may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable laws, respond to legal process, or where DomainPeople has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure.
DomainPeople also will not disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that DomainPeople stores or transmits for its customers except where: (a) it is a matter or public safety or policy; (b) it is in connection with the transfer of other business assets; (c) it is required to cooperate with orders, warrants, or other legal process that DomainPeople determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and (d) it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by DomainPeople and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.
DomainPeople disclaims any intention to censor, edit, or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. DomainPeople will, however, review, delete, or block access to communications that may harm DomainPeople, its customers or third parties. The grounds on which DomainPeople may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of the TOU.
Please note that DomainPeople may use this information collected to direct service notices as well as provide you with other general information that may be of interest to you and information about our services or product offerings that you have opted to receive, as well as other important information regarding your account or services at our discretion. You may not opt our of receiving service related email communications.
Customers may opt out of receiving newsletters and/or promotional emails from DomainPeople by sending a request to newsletter-unsubscribe@domainpeople.com, by using the unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional communication, or by changing your email preferences on the site within your Account information. In this request, customers must identify their domain name and contact information. Customers may not opt out of receiving
information from DomainPeople which is essential for maintaining or updating customers account or system information.
Third Party Advertising and Cookies
The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze Web traffic, improve the content of our website and improve your experience on our website.
We do not trade, rent or sell your personal information to others, except as detailed in this Policy. We currently contract with several online partners who use the data only on our behalf to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Action Tags and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The information collected by the marketing company through the use of Action Tags and cookies is not personally identifiable. We have no access or control over these third party cookies or action tags. The information they collect and share with us helps us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used.
We use other third parties to provide credit card processing services on our site. When you purchase a service or product from us we will share contact and credit card information as necessary for the third party to provide that service.
These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing services.
We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a website can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a Web application to respond to you as an individual. Our cookies are tied to your personally identifiable informant for this purpose. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the Web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Most Web browsers allow you to control this use of cookies. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you elect to disable cookies, please keep in mind that you will not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience on our website. It is possible that some portions of the site will not function properly or may perform more slowly if you choose to reject cookies.
Our website may allow for a chat function. Chat functions allow you to participate in “live” online conversations with us on our website. Although the transcripts from the chats may be stored internally on in-house servers for our records only, we collect no personally identifiable information about you when you participate unless you choose to provide that information to us.
How Can I access my personal information?
You can access your personal information, such as your address and contact information, at anytime to correct, change or delete any of the data shared with us when you became a customer of DomainPeople. As a customer of DomainPeople you can access your personal information by clicking on the “Customer Login” link at the top of any Web page. Your account information is secure and is accessible by using a password that you select. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information you can contact us via email at support@domainpeople.com. DomainPeople will respond to access requests within 30 days.
Security
DomainPeople has security measures in place to help prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When you place an order online, your information, including your credit card number, is protected using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. This encrypts order data and is designed to aid in ensuring the accuracy and security of that customer information.
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If you have any questions about security on our website, you can send email us at support@domainpeople.com
Links
Our website provides links to other websites, sites that may be maintained by companies that are not affiliates of ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and we encourage you to use caution. In particular, we recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each site to confirm the sites policies are acceptable to you. This Policy applies solely to information collected by this website.
Children’s Privacy
DomainPeople does not sell products or services for purchase by children. Customers must be at least 18 years of age. Any individual under the age of 18 (“Minor”) must have a parent or guardian accept the TOU in order for the Minor to become a Customer. If you are under 18, we strongly encourage you to use our website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.
Changes to our Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the primary homepage for DomainPeople, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a prominent notice on our home page.
Contact Us
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should contact us by email at support@domainpeople.com.
The fastest growing ccTLD. Get a new .CO - 1st year only 12.95!
Register Your .CO
.INFO 1st Year Discount
Provide Information with .INFO! Get your's now only $14.95!
Get Started Now
Huge Savings on .CA
Show
your Canadian presence with .ca domains. Best value at $14.95
Order .CA
.MOBI 1st Year Discount
Tap into millions of mobile divices. - 1st year only $12.95!
DomainPeople. All rights reserved. Privacy Statement | Terms of Use | Report Abuse
